<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<suppressions xmlns="https://jeremylong.github.io/DependencyCheck/dependency-suppression.1.3.xsd">
  <!-- Below are the supressions added fpr False Positive CVEs -->
  <suppress until="2022-09-30">
    <notes>The CVE-2018-1258 and CVE-2021-22112 occurs from spring security libraries, despite the latest versions are used. This is confirmed as false positive
      and hence it is suppressed (https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/2952)
    </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2018-1258</cve>
  </suppress>


  <suppress until="2022-09-30">
    <notes> False positive reported at https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/1658.
      The Build fails with newer versions of the library
    </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2007-1651</cve>
    <cve>CVE-2007-1652</cve>
  </suppress>

  <suppress until="2022-09-30">
    <notes><![CDATA[
            This CVE is related to file type tag parsing. However, the associated CVE seems to be a false positive on the lang-tag jar.
            (https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/3043). The CVE occurs in the newer version.
        ]]></notes>
    <cve>CVE-2020-29242</cve>
    <cve>CVE-2020-29243</cve>
    <cve>CVE-2020-29244</cve>
    <cve>CVE-2020-29245</cve>
  </suppress>

  <suppress until="2022-09-30">
    <notes>CVE-2021-28170 https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2021-28170
      Spring Framework vulnerability, subject to review after Spring Boot upgrade to 2.4.x affected lib org.glassfish:jakarta.el:3.0.3
    </notes>
    <cve>CVE-2021-28170</cve>
  </suppress>

   <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>A vulnerability in all versions of Nim-lang allows unauthenticated attackers to write files to
            arbitrary directories via a crafted zip file with dot-slash characters included in the name of the
            crafted file
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-23171</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>Major liquibase update to version 4.8.0+ needed, this will require code refactoring</notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-0839</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>jackson-databind issue, upgrading to new version broke functional tests.</notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-36518</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
      <notes>org.apache.poi issue, upgrading to new version and a large depth of nested objects</notes>
      <cve>CVE-2022-26336</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
      <notes>spring boot issue, upgrading to new version broke functional tests.</notes>
      <cve>CVE-2022-22965</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
      <notes>Spring Framework older unsupported versions, it is possible for a user to provide a specially
        crafted SpEL expression that may cause a denial of service condition</notes>
      <cve>CVE-2022-22950</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
      <notes>In Spring Framework versions 5.3.0 - 5.3.16 and older unsupported versions, it is possible for a user to
        provide a specially crafted SpEL expression that may cause a denial of service condition.
      </notes>
      <cve>CVE-2016-1000027</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
      <notes>In Spring Framework versions 5.3.0 - 5.3.18, 5.2.0 - 5.2.20, and older unsupported versions, the patterns for
        disallowedFields on a DataBinder are case sensitive which means a field is not effectively protected unless it is
        listed with both upper and lower case for the first character of the field, including upper and lower case for the
        first character of all nested fields within the property path.
      </notes>
      <cve>CVE-2022-22968</cve>
    </suppress>
  <!-- Supression Group ends here -->
</suppressions>


